A Guide to the John D. Rockefeller papers FA002
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence, C; 34.4 cubic ft. 86 boxes
  - Business, B; 8.4 cubic ft. 21 boxes
    - McCune - McGowan, 89.0 pages (Reel 7, Frame 0803, Box 61, Folder 450)
      McCune, E. J., 9/6/1887. Shippensburg, Pennsylvania. Mexican oil lands. McCurdy, W. H., 2/121/1889. Cleveland, Ohio. Standard Oil Trust stock purchase. McDermott, I., 4/3/1888. Meadville, Pennsylvania. Job applicant. McDonald, A., 1881-1891. Cincinnati, Ohio. Sales and competition; no fear of Sherman antitrust bill. McDonald, S. A., 1885-1888. Cleveland, Ohio. Refined oil sales and shipments. McDonald, W. H., 7/17/1890. Washington, D. C. West Virginia coal lands. McEwan, G. c., 5/14/1883. Rutherford, New Jersey. Oil shortage tank. McEwan, T. M., 11/22/1882. Jersey City, New Jersey. Job applicant. McGechin, T. H., 1881-1882. Baltimore, Maryland. Sending trial balances. McGee, J. A., 1880-1886. New York, New York. Case Oil pool - Devoe Manufacturing Company. McGee, W. M., 1881-1888. New York, New York. Sending Atlas or Imperial Oil. McGowan, J. M., 7/13/1890. New York, New York. Oil lands.
    - McGregor, A. M., 1877-March 1878; 112.0 pages (Reel 7, Frame 0892, Box 61, Folder 451)
      New York, New York. Production and distribution of refined products; contract relations between units of trust; personnel changes; maintenance of production facilities; activities of competition.
    - McGregor, A. M., April 1878-March 1882; 105.0 pages (Reel 7, Frame 1004, Box 61, Folder 452)
    - McGregor, A. M., April 1882-1886; 99.0 pages (Reel 8, Frame 0001, Box 61, Folder 453)
    - McGregor, A. M., February 1888-January 1893; 67.0 pages (Box 61, Folder 454, Reel 8, Frame 0100)
    - McIntosh - Miller, 138.0 pages (Box 61, Folder 455, Reel 8, Frame 0167)
      McIntosh, D., 1877-1891. Oil City, Pennsylvania. Competitors' sales. McJunkin & Campbell, 2/22/1878. Butler, Pennsylvania. Legal fees -- Tagler suit. McKee, John, 1890. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Oil lands. McKee, J. A., 12/26/1887. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. Sale of refinery. McKee, J. C., 7/6/1889. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. Loan of refinery. McKelvy, W. M., 1878-1888. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. Central Refining Company; Standard Oil Company of Pittsburgh; dissatisfaction with policies of Standard Oil Company. McKennon, G. E., 3/11/1890. Columbia, Tennessee. Job applicant. Mellon, L. F., 2/22/1881. West Springfield, Massachusetts. Job applicant. Mengel, E. H., 1889. Washington, Pennsylvania. Job applicant. Mercer, M. H., 2/17/1888. New York, New York. Job applicant. Merkle, J. F., 11/30/1888. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. Job applicant. Merrill, A. M., 1889. Somerville, Massachusetts. Job applicant. Merrill, F. J., 1883. Bergen, New York. Loan applicant. Merthyr, L., 7/1/1889. Bowen, London, England. Job applicant. Metcalf, L. G., 6/13/1892. Monmouth, Maine. Job applicant. Meyer, E. S., 5/31/1887. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Miller, C., 1880-1883. Franklin, Pennsylvania. Job applicant. Miller, C. J., 3/14/1889. Marion, Pennsylvania. Job applicant. Miller, H., 2/12/1889. New York, New York. Job applicant. Miller, H. L., 10/22/1886. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Miller, J. H., 12/1/1887. Chicago, Illinois. Employee grievance. Miller, R. S., 10/6/1878. New York, New York. Job applicant. Miller, W. J., 10/3/1888. Beaver, Pennsylvania. New type oil tank.
    - Milne - Murray, 69.0 pages (Box 61, Folder 456, Reel 8, Frame 0305)
      Milne, M., 1/31/1888. New York, New York. Job applicant. Miner, J. C., 5/29/1890. Oakland, California. Oil lands. Minke, A. J., 1/26/1889. Freedom, Pennsylvania. Freedom Oil Works for sale. Mitchell, E. O., 6/6/1889. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Moffett, J. A., 1891. Chicago, Illinois. Whiting production. Moon, E. S., 4/24/1886. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Mooney & Boland, undated. New York, New York. Detective agency. Mooney, W. J., 6/18/1885. Bellefontaine, Ohio. Natural gas works. Moore, C. S., 1890. Cleveland, Ohio. Standard Oil Trust stock purchase. Moore, H. S., 8/11/1888. Gadsden, Alabama. Job applicant. Morgan, C., 6/1/1885. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Morgan, H., 6/6/1881. New York, New York. Jersey shore land for sale. Morris, L., 1885. Oil City, Pennsylvania. Interview. Morrison, E., 1881. Harrisburg, Pennsylvania. Job applicant. Morse, W. M., 1/25/1890. Marietta, Ohio. Marietta as center for industry. Morse, O. C., 1883. Cleveland, Ohio. Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA). Morton, F. T., 1885-1887. boston, Massachusetts. Soap ingredient manufacturer. Morton, G. B., 3/7/1887. Baltimore, Maryland. Charter for sale. Morton, W. J., 7/24/1888. Chicago, Illinois. Job applicant. Mosier, M. I., 5/31/1888. New York, New York. Job applicant. Mott, E. H., 1882-1883. New York, New York. News releases. Mott, W. H., 3/1/1888. New York, New York. Job applicant. Motter, J. V., 1882. Havana, Cuba. Job applicant. Moulton, A. J., 12/3/1883. Nashville, Tennessee. Job applicant. Murray, C. M., 5/6/1887. Bradford, Pennsylvania. Job applicant. Murray, G. W., 10/4/1890. New York, New York. Trusts. Murray, J. E., 9/11/1889. New York, New York. Job applicant.
    - N, 37.0 pages (Box 62, Folder 457, Reel 8, Frame 0374)
      National Gas and Water Company, undated. Chicago, Illinois. New process. National Gas Trust, 1893-1894. New York, New York. Dividends. Nehama, J., 4/29/1887. Antwerp, Netherlands. Salonika market. Nelson & Richardson, 3/13/1885. Washington, D. C. Offering refinery. Newell, J., 4/8/1879. Cleveland, Ohio. Refuses railroad pass; Lake Shore & Michigan Southern Railway. Newell, W. J., 1882. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Lobbyist in Pennsylvania. Newton, S., 11/25/1885. Marietta, Ohio. Interview. Northrup, G. W., 1883-1888. Morgan Park, Illinois. Morgan Park Academy; job for son. Northrup, H. W., 2/8/1886. Corfa, New York. Standard Oil Trust stock. Northrup, R. F., 11/30/1888. New York, New York. Job applicant. Norton, W. H., 1887-1892. Allentown, New York. Job applicant. Nuttall, g., 1887-1889. Springfield, Massachusetts. Job applicant.
    - Oakley - O'Day, D., 108.0 pages (Reel 8, Frame 0411, Box 62, Folder 458)
      Oakley, T. H., 6/6/1885. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. O'Day, D., 1877-February 1880. Bradford and Titusville, Pennsylvania, and Buffalo and New York, New York. Pipeline management; United Pipe Lines; American Transfer Company; negotiations with producers and shippers; Tidewater Pipe Company; National Transit Company; natural gas business.
    - O'Day, D., 1880-1882; 102.0 pages (Reel 8, Frame 0519, Box 62, Folder 459)
      Bradford and Titusville, Pennsylvania, and Buffalo and New York, New York. Pipeline management; United Pipe Lines; American Transfer Company; negotiations with producers and shippers; Tidewater Pipe Company; National Transit Company; natural gas business.
    - O'Day, D., 1883-July 1886; 103.0 pages (Reel 8, Frame 0621, Box 62, Folder 460)
    - O'Day, D., August 1886-1893; 104.0 pages (Reel 8, Frame 0724, Box 62, Folder 461)
    - O'Dorman - Owstron, 53.0 pages (Box 62, Folder 462, Reel 8, Frame 0828)
      O'Dorman, T. C., 8/1/1889. Putnam, Pennsylvania. Job applicant. Ohlen, H. C., 1880. New York, New York. Negotiations with Mr. Bush. Oliver, C. C., 10/1/1886. Boston, Indiana. Job applicant. Oliver, J. B., 1890. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. Buys Standard Oil Company products; wants Standard Oil Company iron business. Olmsted, M. E., 1881. Harrisburg, Pennsylvania. Purchase of Southern Railway Securities Company; Pennsylvania taxes. Omeara, C. J., 6/17/1887. Green Island, New York. Job applicant. Oppenheim, L., 5/3/1878. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. Job applicant. Osborn, C. J., 3/6/1888. New York, New York. Job applicant. Osborn, T. L., 1885. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Osborne, D., 10/4/1893. Chicago, Illinois. Laundry proposal. Osborne, H., 3/18/1879. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Osborne, J. A., 3/2/1887. Cleveland, Ohio. Toledo dock property. Ostrander, W. H., 7/23/1887. Troy, New York. Job applicant. Overbeck, H. F., 1890. Toledo, Ohio. Job applicant. Owstron, C. W., 1888-1892. Cleveland, Ohio. Fuel oil department.
    - Paddock - Payne, 82.0 pages (Box 62, Folder 463, Reel 8, Frame 0881)
      Paddock, C. H., 2/9/1890. Belle Isle, New York. Extracting sulphur. Paine, S. H., 1879-1893. New York, New York. Lubricating department manager; operations of subsidiary companies; dissatisfaction with regional arrangements of sales. Paintor, K. V., 9/15/1893. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Palmer, E. C., 7/4/1890. Prairie Depot, Ohio. Job applicant. Parke, T. H., 1/31/1892. New York, New York. Real estate. Parkhurst, R. W., 5/3/1889. Clyde, Ohio. Job applicant. Parks, H. F., 8/14/1888. Salem, Ohio. Job applicant. Parsons, R. C., 12/4/1879. Cleveland, Ohio. Herald Publishing Company. Paskins, J. B., 3/18/1887. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Patterson, A. S., 1887-1890. New York, New York. Auditor. Patterson, S. L., 1880-1882. Reports on Western Union bills. Patterson, S. Louise, 5/22/1886. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Patton, B., 12/30/1887. Fontland, Ohio. Oil lands. Paxton, G. P., 4/8/1890. New York, New York. Job applicant. Payne, C. N., 1892. Oil City, Pennsylvania. Employee assistance; general manager, United Pipe Lines; National Transit Company. Payne, H. R., 1881-1887. Cleveland, Ohio. Standard Oil Company accountant.
    - Payne, O. H., November 1877-November 1879; 95.0 pages (Box 63, Folder 464, Reel 8, Frame 0963)
      Cleveland, Ohio. Treasurer, Standard Oil Company; reports on competition; purchase of crude oil; purchases of refineries; legislative action; private salaries.
    - Payne, O. H., December 1879-March 1881; 111.0 pages (Box 63, Folder 465, Reel 9, Frame 0001)
    - Payne, O. H., April 1881-April 1883; 108.0 pages (Reel 9, Frame 0112, Box 63, Folder 466)
    - Payne, O. H., May 1883-March 1889; 111.0 pages (Reel 9, Frame 0220, Box 63, Folder 467)
    - Pearne - Pyle, 160.0 pages (Reel 9, Frame 0331, Box 63, Folder 468)
      Pearne, B. D., 5/22/1889. Lancaster, Ohio. Gas lands. Peck, C. C., 1883. Bermuda. Employee assistance. Pell, W. T., 1888. New York, New York. Job applicant. Perdue, E. H., 4/7/1882. Cleveland, Ohio. Sale of refinery to Standard Oil Company. Perkins, C. A., 3/17/1893. New York, New York. George Rice suit. Perkins, D. P., 11/29/1886. Portland, Maine. Job applicant. Perkins, J., 10/12/1883. Cleveland, Ohio. Woman's Christian Temperance Union. Peters, R. G., 2/19/1887. Manistee, Michigan. Job applicant. Pherson, T. J., 11/28/1888. New York, New York. Employee assistance. Phillips, C. W., 5/21/1889. New York, New York. Job applicant. Phinney, C. L., 12/6/1888. New York, New York. Job applicant. Phinney, E. J., 7/15/1889. Cleveland, Ohio. Woman's Christian Temperance Union Fund. Pielsticker, C. A., 2/18/1882. London, England. Oil lands. Pierce, H. C., 1881-1890. St. Louis, Missouri. Waters Pierce Oil Company; personnel matters. Poe, A. S., 5/11/1888. Ravenna, Ohio. Job applicant. Pomeroy, C. S., 4/28/1886. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Pond, L., 6/23/1888. St. Paris, Ohio. Job applicant. Poole, W. T., 1881. Baltimore, Maryland. Camden Consolidated Oil Company. Pooler, F. W., 10/28/1891. New York, New York. Elevated pipeline. Porter, A., 1886. New York, New York. Job applicant. Porter, W. D., 1888. New York, New York. Job applicant. Potter, D. C., 1883. New York, New York. Sixth St. Baptist Church gift. Potter, H. C., 4/3/1889. Minneapolis, Minnesota. Job applicant. Pouch, A. J., 1880-1885. New York, New York. Tin plate supplies; Standard Oil Company of New York, French contract; J. A. Bostwick & Company; oil manufacturing and sales. Poultney, T., 1878-1881. Baltimore, Maryland. Baltimore United Oil Company. Pratt, C., 1877-1890. Vassar College scholarship; Pratt Manufacturing Company; merchandising, manufacturing, and speculation. Standard Oil Trust trustee responsibilities. Preble, B. B., 9/25/1886. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Prentiss, C., 11/19/1884. Cleveland, Ohio. Coal for sale. Price, W. B., 1886-1888. Newark, New Jersey. Job applicant. Priestly, E., 3/10/1891. New York, New York. Job applicant. Prindall, C. W., 5/7/1889. Gloucester, Massachusetts. Job applicant. Prindle, H. E., 1/26/1878. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Prytz, C. S., 11/21/1882. New York, New York. Job applicant. Puffenberger, J., 5/7/1887. New York, New York. Job applicant. Pugh & Company, 2/23/1884. Chicago, Illinois. Oil in Canada. Putham, T. L., 2/13/1884. Boston, Massachusetts. Cattle company proposal. Pyle, G. W., 10/13/1883. Mansfield, Ohio. Oil lands.
    - Q, 7.0 pages (Reel 9, Frame 0491, Box 63, Folder 469)
      Quay, G. H., 1879-1880. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Quay, J. J., 10/22/?. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Quinn, A., 1/9/1879. Cleveland, Ohio. Loan on flour mill.
    - Rabone - Rockefeller, B., 78.0 pages (Reel 9, Frame 0498, Box 63, Folder 470)
      Rabone, J., 5/17/1889. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Ralya, J. J., 11/17/1877. Cleveland, Ohio. Interview. Ramaker, 10/18/1886. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Randebaugh, G. S., 6/18/1890. Ness City, Kansas. Job applicant. Rany, A., 1878. Great Belt, Pennsylvania. Would Standard Oil Company unite with the producers? Rawlings, C. M., 2/22/1884. Berea, Ohio. Oil lands. Rawlings, E., 3/17/1891. New York, New York. Bonding Company. Raymond, E., 3/23/1892. Franklin, Pennsylvania. Real estate. Ready, T., 6/25/1888. New York, New York. Job applicant. Reddy, J. 1888. New York, New York. Job applicant. Reed, A. C., 8/23/1888. Chicago, Illinois. Hall refining process. Reed, L. A., 5/5/1890. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Reed, W. A., 4/14/1891. Jamestown, New York. Job applicant. Regelien, H., 3/25/1886. New York, New York. Corporation scheme. Reid, I. D., 1889. New York, New York. Job applicant. Reid, W., 6/14/1892. Paris, France. Introducing French minister. Reste, A. V., 11/1/1881. Cerberi, Belgium. Fibreboard barrels. Reynaud, G. P., 9/13/1893. New York, New York. Job applicant. Rice, C., 12/8/1890. Washington, D. C., New type of pump. Rice, George, 1893. New York, New York. Summons and complaint in Rice suit. Richards, C. B., 10/24/1891. San Diego, California. Oil lands. Richards, M. W., 4/16/1890. Providence, Rhode Island. Job applicant. Ringgold, E., 5/26/1888. New York, New York. Job applicant. Ritchie, S. J., 3/1/1890. Akron, Ohio. Canadian oil fields. Roberts, G. B., 4/9/1880. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Urges cooperation between Standard Oil Company and outside refineries. Robertson, A., 11/10/1887. South Orange, New Jersey. New York oil lands. Robertson, G. T., 11/1/1888. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Robinson, M. A., 1878-1886. New York, New York. Union Tank Car Line -- Erie Canal shipments. Robinson, W. C., 4/26/1889. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Job applicant. Rockafellow, N. E., 7/28/1889. Nottingham, Ohio. Job applicant. Rockefeller, B., 2/11/1889. New York, New York. Job applicant.
    - Rockefeller, Franklin, February 1878-October 1886; 95.0 pages (Reel 9, Frame 0576, Box 64, Folder 471)
      Cleveland, Ohio. Reports on sales and manufacturing; competitors' activities; conflicts between units of Standard Oil Trust; pricing policies; intra-company rebates.
    - Rockefeller, Franklin, December 1886-March 1887; 93.0 pages (Reel 9, Frame 0671, Box 64, Folder 472)
    - Rockefeller, Franklin, April 1887-January 1888; 81.0 pages (Reel 9, Frame 0764, Box 64, Folder 473)
    - Rockefeller, Franklin, February-April 1888; 64.0 pages (Box 64, Folder 474, Reel 9, Frame 0845)
    - Rockefeller, Franklin, May-September 1888; 96.0 pages (Box 64, Folder 475, Reel 9, Frame 0909)
    - Rockefeller, Franklin, October-December 1888; 84.0 pages (Box 64, Folder 476, Reel 10, Folder 0001)
    - Rockefeller, Franklin, January-April 1889; 88.0 pages (Box 65, Folder 477, Reel 10, Frame 0085)
    - Rockefeller, Franklin, May-December 1889; 91.0 pages (Box 65, Folder 478, Reel 10, Frame 0173)
    - Rockefeller, Franklin, January-July 1890; 87.0 pages (Box 65, Folder 479, Reel 10, Folder 0264)
    - Rockefeller, Franklin, August 1890-February 1891; 86.0 pages (Box 65, Folder 480, Reel 10, Frame 0351)
    - Rockefeller, Franklin, March 1891-July 1893; 106.0 pages (Box 65, Folder 481, Reel 10, Frame 0437)
    - Rockefeller, J. R. - Rockefeller, John D., 153.0 pages (Reel 10, Frame 0543, Box 65, Folder 482)
      Rockefeller, J. R., 9/15/1890. Poughkeepsie, New York. Job applicant. Rockefeller, John D. 1880-1891. Cleveland, Ohio, and New York, New York. Defense of Standard Oil Trust; quality of oil.
    - Rockefeller, John D., 1892-1893; 60.0 pages (Reel 10, Frame 0696, Box 65, Folder 483)
      Cleveland, Ohio, and New York, New York. Defense of Standard Oil Trust; quality of oil.
    - Rockefeller, W. J. - Rogers, George D., 72.0 pages (Reel 10, Frame 0756, Box 66, Folder 484)
      Rockefeller, W. J., 10/19/1889. Hartford Mills, New York. Job applicant. Rockefeller, William, 1883-1890. New York, New York. Trust stock and oil certificates. Rodway, E., 12/11/1877. Newburgh, Ohio. Job applicant. Roe, L., 1885-1890. New York, New York. Petroleum newsletter. Rogers, George D., 1881-1891. Cleveland, Ohio, and New York, New York. John D. Rockefeller's private secretary; vacations; letters of transmittal; personal matters; stocks and bonds.
    - Rogers, Henry H. - Russell, 57.0 pages (Reel 10, Frame 0828, Box 66, Folder 485)
      Rogers, Henry H., 1880-1890. New York, New York. Pumps, Tidewater Pipe Company; Lombard, Ayres & Company trade; Pratt Manufacturing Company; National Transit Company. Root, C. T., 1/2/1883. New York, New York. Urges defense of Standard Oil Company. Rose, C. W., 2/18/1884. New York, New York. Job applicant. Ross, G. E., 2/11/1891. New York, New York. Job applicant. Round, W. M., 10/15/1883. New York, New York. Prison Association of New York. Rowan, D. N., 3/31/1882. New York, New York. Real estate. Rowand, A. G., 4/8/1879. Allegheny, Pennsylvania. New oil burner. Rowland, D. H., 2/7/1888. New York, New York. Financial information. Rowley, W. J., 12/9/1886. New York, New York. Job applicant. Rundebrook, O., 2/9/1893. Rotterdam, Netherlands. American Petroleum Company. Russell, G. B., 5/10/1889. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Russell, H. P., 1890. Westfield, New Jersey. Job applicant. Russell, L. W., 5/10/1886. New York, New York. Job applicant.
    - Sackett - Scheide, 98.0 pages (Reel 10, Frame 0885, Box 66, Folder 486)
      Sackett, H. A., 1/11/1887. Meadville, Pennsylvania. Job applicant. St. Goar, H., 12/24/1892. New York, New York. Job applicant. Sampson, W., 10/20/1883. New York, New York. Industrial school. Samuel, D. M., 2/5/1887. La Junta, Colorado. Job applicant. Sander, G. W., 1889. Jolly Po, Ohio. Oil lands. Sanders, H. L., 12/6/1890. New York, New York. Job applicant. Sanderland, B., 11/3/1887. Washington, D. C. Job applicant. Sandford, T. L., 12/8/1888. New York, New York. Job applicant. Sanford, N., 10/27/1886. Scott, Kansas. Job applicant. Sargent, W. P., 1890-1892. Cleveland, Ohio. Frank Rockefeller's secretary. Sawyer, N. P., 1879. Cleveland, Ohio. Mr. Smith's Gas works. Scheide, W. T., 1881-1889. Oil City, Pennsylvania. United Pipe Lines policies; National Transit Company; competitors' blackmail; construction cost of oil.
    - Schmid - "Servant", 76.0 pages (Reel 11, Frame 0001, Box 66, Folder 487)
      Schmid, P., 1878-1890. New York, New York. Standard Oil Company employee; 1879 oil trade resume; Austrian oil trade; home trade statistics. Schneebeli, G. A., 4/24/1879. Andenried, Pennsylvania. Job applicant. Schuary, J. G., 2/19/1889. Brightswood, Indiana. Gas wells. Schultheis, P., 4/20/1890. New York, New York. Tanks for sale. Schumacher, W., 3/10/1878. Detroit, Michigan. Job applicant. Schweichert, C., 3/5/1888. New York, New York. Job applicant. Scofield, Shurmer & Teagle, 1881-1888. Cleveland, Ohio. Outside refineries; brief on railroad discrimination; in favor of Standard Oil Company. Scott, C. W., 7/31/1889. Jackson, Mississippi. Job applicant. Scott, J., 4/7/1880. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Compromise with Mr. Sherasaul and Mr. Ohlen. Scudder, H., 3/17/1880. New York, New York. Legislative lobbyist. Seddon, H. J., 1/29/1890. New York, New York. Job applicant. See, E. D., 9/17/1883. Olean, New York. First Baptist Church. Seep, J., 1881-1890. Oil City, Pennsylvania. Oil markets. Segur, G. W., 1887-1889. New York, New York. Job applicant. Seiler, V. I., 1891-1892. Cleveland, Ohio. Western Union bills. "Servant," 5/12/1887. Bradford, Pennsylvania. Producer's complaint.
    - Severance, L. H., 1879-1893; 75.0 pages (Reel 11, Frame 0077, Box 66, Folder 488)
      Cleveland, Ohio. Cashier and treasurer, Standard Oil of Ohio; avoiding subpoenas; stock transfers; summary cost and profit figures.
    - Severance, L. H. - Telegrams, 1885-1893; 66.0 pages (Reel 11, Frame 0152, Box 66, Folder 489)
    - Seville - Small, 113.0 pages (Box 66, Folder 490, Reel 11, Frame 0218)
      Seville, A. B., 4/7/1890. Washington, D. C. Oil lands. Sexton, J., 3/10/1886. New York, New York. Job applicant. Seymour, H. B., 11/5/1877. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Shaddle, C. V., 3/10/1884. New York, New York. Job applicant. Shafer, E. L., 1885. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Shafer, V., 1/25/1878. Cleveland, Ohio. National Guard unit. Shanck, H. K., 7/30/1892. Cleveland, Ohio. Gasoline engine for street cars. Shaw, J. W., 10/19/1886. Bradford, Pennsylvania. Job applicant. Shaw, John, 1884. Rochester, New York. Information on wire tapping. Shaw, W. A., 1/12/1887. New York, New York. Job applicant. Sheaff, L., 1/16/1893. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Sheldon, G. E., 3/12/1888. Phenn, Rhode Island. Job applicant. Sheley, G. A., 10/17/1888. Detroit, Michigan. Gas franchise. Shepard, C. D., undated. Maysville, Kentucky. Job applicant. Sheppard, W. J., 7/9/1892. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Sherman, W. W., 5/20/1886. New York, New York. Interview. Short, J. C., 10/11/1887. New York, New York. Railroad and petroleum interests. Shotwell, J., 1887-1890. New York, New York. Job applicant. Shreve, W. T., 8/10/1888. Tulare, Colorado. Job applicant. Sickels, D. B., 4/25/1883. New York, New York. Job applicant. Sill, J. E., 5/26/1889. New York, New York. Job applicant. Simmons, C. G., 1891. New York, New York. Job applicant. Simmons, E. B., 6/14/1889. Baltimore, Maryland. Job applicant. Simmons, F., 2/3/1891. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Simmons, James B., 10/13/1883. New York, New York. Church gift. Simmons, J. H., 4/12/1879. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant. Simmons, T., 1879-1890. Cleveland, Ohio. Job applicant; Solar Refining Company production. Simpson, J. A., 10/17/1887. New York, New York. Job applicant. Sked, C. P., 7/2/1893. New York, New York. Job applicant. Skilton, C. C., 11/21/1890. New York, New York. Check perforator. Skinner, C. R., 8/18/1890. Washington, D. C. Job applicant. Skinner, E. A., 2/1/1881. Cleveland, Ohio. Job protection. Skinner, M. M., 11/3/1882. Cleveland, Ohio. Purchase Standard Oil Trust certificates. Small, E., 1885. New York, New York. New type of can machine.
    - Smith - Springer, 74.0 pages (Box 66, Folder 491, Reel 11, Frame 0331)